ourproperties.com.au 2017-02-16

# Privacy - Market and Sell Your Australia Real Estate Properties, Land and Homes to China, Chinese Property Buyers, Chinese Property Investors - ourproperties.com.au

**1\. Introduction**

www.OurProperties.com.au ("the web site") is a web site of GiFang Group Pty Ltd and its related companies ("We", "our" and "us" in this Privacy Policy). By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of the web site, which is set out below. The Privacy Policy relates to the collection and use of personal information you may supply to us through your conduct on the web site.

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. This Privacy Policy is in addition to any other terms and conditions applicable to the web site or our other web sites. We do not make any representations about third party web sites that may be linked to the web site.

We recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors to our sites, in particular information that is capable of identifying an individual ("personal information") and relevant real estate properties. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which your personal information, obtained through the web site, will be dealt with. By using the web site, or entering into an agreement with us in relation to the website or any of our other websites you are taken to have read, and agreed to the collection, use, disclosure and handling of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. We welcome your comments and feedback.

**2\. Information We Receive**

**Information you provide to us:**

**Information About Yourself.** We manage personal information obtained through or displayed on the web site or otherwise provided by real estate agents, real estate developers or visitors to the web site. When you sign up for the web site you provide us with your name, email, and phone number. You will also be able to add a picture of yourself. In some cases we may ask for additional information for security reasons or to provide specific services to you. Once you register you can provide other information about yourself, for example, your current city, office address, preference for purchase and investment, and stories about you and/or your properties. We may also ask you for personal information if you report a problem with the website or willing to provide feedback and/or complaints. 

**Privacy Act.** In collecting and handling personal information, we are bound by the Commonwealth Privacy Act 1988, including the National Privacy Principles, and any other applicable privacy laws in Australia. In conjunction with our multi-lingual websites for the purpose of attracting buying interests internationally, there may be circumstances in which we need to transfer personal information outside Australia. If we do so, we strive to ensure that any organisation to which the information is transferred will be subject to binding privacy obligations.

**Content.** One of the primary reasons people use the web site is to share content with others. Examples include when you update the status of your property(s), add or remove a property, upload or record a video on your property, share a link, create an event or a group, make a comment, write a note, or send someone a message. If you do not want us to store metadata associated with content you share on the web site (such as photos), please remove the metadata before uploading the content.

**Transactional Information.** We may retain the details of transactions or payments you make on the web site. If you do not want us to store your payment source account number, you can contact us via details on the ‘contact us’ page. 

**Friend Information.** We may offer contact importer tools to help you upload your friends’ email addresses so that you can invite your contacts who do not have the web site accounts to join. This is optional. If you give us your password to retrieve those contacts, we will not store your password after you have uploaded your contacts’ information.

**Information we collect when you interact with the web site:**

**Site activity information.** We keep track of some of the actions you take on the web site, such as attending an event, uploading a photo, submitting an inquiry, or connecting with an application. In some cases you are also taking an action when you provide information or content to us. For example, if you share a property article, in addition to storing the actual content you uploaded, we might log the fact that you shared it.

**Access Device and Browser Information.** When you access the web site from a computer, mobile phone, or other device, we may collect information from that device about your browser type, location, and IP address, as well as the pages you visit.

**Cookie Information.** Cookies are data that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are industry standard and are used by most Web sites, including those operated by us, can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. They allow us to customise the web site to your needs. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. But you should note that Cookies may be necessary to provide you with some features of our on-line services.

**Information we receive from third parties:**

**Web site Platform.** We do not own or operate the applications or web sites that you use through the web site Platform (such as widgets and utilities). Whenever you connect with a platform application or web site, we will receive information from them, including information about actions you take. In some cases, in order to personalize the process of connecting, we may receive a limited amount of information even before you connect with the application or web site.

**Information from other web sites.** We may institute programs with advertising partners and other web sites in which they share information with us:

• We may ask advertisers to tell us how our users responded to the ads we showed them (and for comparison purposes, how other users who didn’t see the ads acted on their site). This data sharing, commonly known as “conversion tracking,” helps us measure our advertising effectiveness and improve the quality of the advertisements you see.

• We may receive information about whether or not you’ve seen or interacted with certain ads on other sites in order to measure the effectiveness of those ads.

If in any of these cases we receive data that we do not already have, we will stop associating the information with any particular user. If we institute these programs, we will only use the information in the ways we explain in the “Use Your Information” section below.

**Information from other users.** We may collect information about you from other OurProperties users, such as one that is attending your open inspections, auctions, adding you as a syndicate partner, or indicates a relationship with you.

Personal information about visitors to our sites is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with further services or to answer or forward any requests or enquiries. It is our intention that this policy will protect your personal information from being dealt with in any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in Australia.

**Use of Information**

Personal information that visitors submit to our sites is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted or for such other secondary purposes that are related to the primary purpose, unless we disclose other uses in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. Copies of correspondence sent from the web site, that may contain personal information, are stored as archives for record-keeping and back-up purposes only. You should be aware that providing information to a real estate agent through our site will result in the information being passed to the real estate agent and your information will then be held subject to the privacy obligations of the real estate agent which may not conform with this Privacy Policy.

We may share your information with our service providers and other third parties so that they can contact you and provide you with information about offers, promotions, goods or services. If we do use your personal information in these ways, we will always give you the opportunity to request that your information not be used for further direct marketing in the future.

We may also use personal information to help you verify your account, notify you about changes to our service and remind you of your password and username.

**Disclosure**

Apart from where you have consented or disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was submitted, personal information may be disclosed in special situations where we have reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. Also, we may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires disclosure.

We may engage third parties to provide you with goods or services on our behalf. In that circumstance, we may disclose your personal information to those third parties in order to meet your request for goods or services. 

**Security**

We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our sites, and we review and update our security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. 

However, we will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. Once we do receive your transmission, we will also make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, we will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.

All sub-domains of the website, including but not limited to sub-domains of [www.OurProperties.com.au](http://ourproperties.com.au/) and other websites, may be branded as products and/or services of third parties and we will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information. 

**Data Processing and Analysis**

Like many web site operators, we also use the independent company Google (Google Analytics) to measure and analyse the internet usage across our web sites. Google Analytics is a leader in the internet industry in interactive measurement technologies. We use Google Analytics services to collect the following core information on the usage of our web sites, including but not limited to: 

• The number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on our web sites;   
• The number of unique browsers to our web sites;   
• Location data, weblogs and other communication data and resources you access;   
• How long these unique browsers (on average) spend on our web sites when they do visit;   
• Common entry and exit points into our web sites. 

This aggregate, non-personal information is collated by Google Analytics and provided to us to assist in analysing the usage of our web sites. The Google Analytics data may also be accessible by media organizations and research companies, for the purpose of conducting industry comparisons with other Internet portals.

All pages on our web sites are coded with software provided by Google Analytics that stores a "cookie" in the browser, which contains a unique identifier. This enables Google Analytics to track the number of unique browsers to our web sites. This information is collected and aggregated by Google Analytics, and in no way does this unique identifier identify a user personally. We do not and will not marry any data collected by Google Analytics with any personal information collected on our web sites.

Google Analytics software code cannot be disabled entirely on our web sites, as Google Analytics code takes into account all web-browser configurations, including the disabling of Java and Javascript. Google Analytics’ methods of measuring unique visitors takes into account the proportion of visitors who have disabled cookies in their browser. To learn more about Google Analytics’ privacy policy, please visit http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html.

**Access to Information**

We will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. If, at any time, you discover that information held about you is incorrect, you may contact us to have the information corrected.

In addition, our employees, partners, and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us.

**Links to other sites**

We provide links to web sites outside of our web sites, as well as to third party web sites. These linked sites are not under our control, and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of companies linked to our web site. Before disclosing your personal information on any other web site, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions of using that web site and its privacy statement.

**Problems or questions**

If we become aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with our web sites, we will take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, please contact us.

**Further Privacy Information**

For more information about privacy issues in Australia and protecting your privacy, visit the [Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner's](http://www.privacy.gov.au/) web site.
